Great, gunshots, perfect.
It's just a backfire.
Yeah, like you'd know.
Face it, man, we are lost.
Hold on a second.
Yeah, we're here, where the hell are you?
Why don't your
bitch ass look behind you
and see what's cracking, man?
I got this.
Let me see it.
Let me see it?
Let me see it, man.
Show him the fucking money.
Show him, show him.
Where is it?
What, you think I got
it in my pocket, man?
- Yeah.
- I can't go get it, man.
Y'all might be the po-po.
I ain't no po-po.
You gonna have to go
get it yourself, man.
It's just around the
corner, down the block,
by the, what's that, nigga?
Loose brick, north side of
the building, motherfucker.
Go on, man, bounce.
Let me go on record, Jason.
This is a really bad idea.
There it is.
Nice.
It's easy as pie.
Twice as tasty.
Man, someone's screwing with my car!
Come on!
Come on, in here!
Saw them go in.
This is a waste of fucking time.
Forget it, there's no
way they're in there.
Hey, trust me.
I've been working down here for 20 years.
There's nobody in there, now let's go.
Fucking donut shop shuts in five minutes.
All right.
Oh, God damn it!
Let's get the hell out of here.
Dude, that was close.
What the fuck was that?
Fuck.
Where'd it go?
I don't care, let's
get the fuck out of here.
- Go, go, go!
- Come on!
What the hell was that?
Get away from there!
Get!
Dude, let's get out of here.
I'm right behind you, man.
Oh, man.
Palmer!
Somebody help me!
For outside are dogs and sorcerers.
Revelation 22, verse 15.
Hey, check it out!
Yeah, yeah, place your
bets, place your bets.
What's your number, what's your number?
What's that number again, baby?
Yeah, it must be your birthday?
Get your money right,
put it in here, baby.
Come on, let's get these numbers running.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
I don't know, this
looks like a damn graveyard
around here, bro.
Come on, man,
this neighborhood's making a comeback.
Well where the hell has it been?
This is the ugliest
building I've ever seen.
Nah, I don't know, I think it's...
Something about this building.
It just drew me.
All right, you know something?
I was planning on doing this
after I got the place
cleaned up and whatnot,
but, like the man says, carpe diem.
So what do you think
about this, little sis?
- That's us.
- Illbient?
Whose club is that?
Ours.
What do you mean, ours?
Like I said, ours.
Come on, come on, check it out.
- In this?
- Yes.
Patrick, what are you thinking?
This is prehistoric.
Can you picture it, though?
Look, we could have the bar right here.
Dance floor.
- Yo, Bill, Bill.
- What, what?
DJ booth, right there.
Anything's possible,
but that's a lot of work.
Oh, Jesus, okay.
Tell me that's part of a dog or something.
- Yeah, that's dog.
- I don't know.
That's from a cat or something.
It's a pretty big cat, Patrick.
Cat, dog, whatever.
I got a really great deal on this place.
I'm talking about a
really great deal, man.
They couldn't give it away!
Dead meat stinking up
their books for 20 years.
Don't do that!
- Maurice, stop playing, man.
- That ain't funny, man.
If I fell...
Chill.
Yo, man, the last owner
on the lease before the bank
was back in '79.
Some cat named Jimmy Bones.
Been empty ever since.
Jimmy Bones?
Yeah, why, you heard of him?
- You haven't?
- No, not that I can remember.
He was a local legend back
in the 70s in this area.
Sure.
There was a song...
Sing it for me, baby, come on.
Let's do this, ready?
Something about a deuce.
A switchblade.
A switchblade and a diamond.
Come get yourself
a couple of dollars
and go buy you a piece
of candy or something.
Say thank you, Uncle Jimmy.
Thank you, Uncle Jimmy.
Jimmy Bones.
Maurice. Jimmy Bones.
How badass is that?
Jimmy Bones!
Oh, Patrick, I'm gonna tell you something.
I'm sold, baby, and
I'm gonna tell you why.
This is what I'm thinking.
We could use this whole Jimmy Bones theme
to make this place off the hook.
Look at this place, man, it's a dump.
No, actually, it'd have
to work to be a dump.
You know something,
you need to take a look
at the rest of the place before
you start tearing it down.
Yeah, man, I know it's cold.
I'm gonna run downstairs,
fire up the furnace,
see if I can warm the joint up
a little bit, and you'll see.
This place has serious potential, man.
Yeah, potential to leave
me seriously injured.
You know, I'm gonna check out
how we gonna get the
DJ equipment up there.
Who's coming?
Aw, man.
Shit.
Am I tripping?
I'm going this way.
Yeah, me too.
No you won't, buddy.
You're gonna follow me upstairs.
Tia, be careful.
Oh, shit!
Fucking rats.
Please don't bust.
Cause I can't afford that.
What's up?
Contact paranoia.
Maybe you heard of it.
I'm bugging out because I'm hanging out
with you all the time.
I tell you, goddamn, man.
Yeah, well I got bigger problems.
I can't get this joint
lit, and that's drug abuse.
Maurice, it
stinks enough down here
without you sparking that up.
The man said
to use my imagination.
Maurice?
Bill?
Hey, buddy.
How long you been locked in here for?
Want my burger?
Damn, you were hungry.
You want us to move in here?
That's the only way
we're gonna get the place fixed in time.
Yeah, right.
And whichever of us is
alive by the end of week
inherits all Vincent Price's cash.
Look, you wanna play college
radio, high school reunions,
and some fool's club once a week
for the rest of your lives, that's cool,
but I think we can do better.
Now I'm putting everything
I got into this,
because I believe we can make it happen.
We move in, we take shifts.
- We call crash together.
- Okay, coach,
enough with the motivational speech.
I'm down, all right?
Thank you.
He has a good track
record, so just go with him.
Yeah, fine.
Mars needs a little bit of Venus.
If I'm gonna sleep in a spook house,
surround me with chicks that
are more scared than me.
Speaking of which.
Why would you say that
about my sister, man?
Oh, shit.
Hey, look who I found.
Tia?
That's the nastiest dog I ever seen.
Well he's not as ugly
as some people I know.
Anyway, I'm naming him Bones.
Bones?
Well look, let's go get the
stuff we need and bring it back.
- Shotgun.
- Shotgun, I said it first.
No, you just hear things late.
By the way.
Dad does know about this, right?
Are you kidding?
- Patrick, man...
- It's gonna be cool, bro,
I'm telling you.
What y'all doing over there with that dog?
Is he yours?
Is he yours, sir?
Hell, no!
What do you care, then?
I'm gonna tell you something, boy.
Shoot that dog.
Shoot the dog?
Whatever you say, sir.
I think it's nappy time.
Come on, Bones.
Nah, Tia, put him in the back.
He's fine, just leave...
Don't feed that dog!
The hell's wrong with you?
Some holes can't be filled,
and some hunger can't be satisfied.
Some people need to
stagger their medication.
I'm serious!
He'll only get hungrier!
Come on, Cynthia, come on.
Y'all people really
don't like dogs, do you?
Ma'am, you need any
help with those bags?
No, thank you.
No, really, let us help.
We just moved into the neighborhood,
we're gonna be neighbors.
No, here, let me help you out.
You moved onto this block?
Yeah.
Well not really to live, but to play.
See, I'm a DJ, right?
In that building?
Yeah, it's gonna be le hot shit.
Pardon my Francais.
We're making it a dance club.
You ever heard of the
Resurrection Brothers?
Should I?
They on the radio?
Nah, but they will be, they're the best.
How do you know?
- I manage them.
- It's us.
And you bought that building?
Yeah.
Wait a minute, you
look a little familiar.
Are you sure you're not from around here?
Well I was born near here,
but after my mom died, Dad moved us out.
I grew up in Rossmore Park.
You're a little dark to be
growing up in Rossmore Park.
Yo, she's fine.
I guess it's not Rossmore Park,
but thanks for the help.
Hey, anytime.
Here.
Well I guess I'll be seeing you, then.
It was nice to meet you.
Yo, if she has psychic powers,
how come she's working
here in Desolation Row?
Come on, man.
What happened to the Colonel?
Gangsta of love don't
eat no fried chicken.
Why not, you eat everything else.
Look, everybody knows
the whole chicken distribution
network is owned by the Klan.
Oh come on, man, don't even go there.
When's the last time you
seen a black chicken farm?
Yeah, special recipe.
I'm telling you, there's
something in the batter
that makes a black man sterile.
- Bullshit!
- Yo, hold up, man.
Why all of the sudden you so concerned
with the plight of the black man?
Last time I checked, you was not black.
I don't know exactly what you are,
but you damn sure ain't no black man.
I am the future, all right?
I am the melting pot.
- You been smoking pot.
- I'm the tossed salad.
I am Martin Luther King's dream.
All I gotta do is hold my own hand.
I am post-racial.
You're post-toasted.
Post-apocalyptic, more like.
You're making my head hurt.
Just eat your food.
Eddie, man, what's wrong, nigga?
Yeah!
How many times I done told y'all, man?
When I'm playing this game
here, don't interrupt me.
We just hooked you up
with a tight Viper, nigga.
We are paid, nigga!
Viper!
A Viper?
A Viper that you stole off them white boys
that was down here last night?
- Yep, yep, yep.
- Like that, nigga.
Just like that.
Are y'all out your motherfucking mind?
- No.
- Man, everybody heard
that damn screaming last
night on Blackstone.
Remember that shit?
That shit?
Man, how many times I done told
you two knucklehead niggers?
No psycho shit.
If there's gonna be any psycho
shit, I'm the one that do it.
We know that, we respect that.
That's why we didn't do shit.
You gonna tell me that
you didn't Ginsu them punks
and steal their ride?
Yeah, steal their
ride, that's all we did.
That's all we did.
Man, get that car the fuck
away from here, you understand?
See, this is the type of shit
I'm talking about, right here.
I pay the pigs good money
to keep this shit cool around
here, and this is the shit
that pisses everybody the fuck off, nigga.
Boy, if I didn't know your mama...
- We just thought...
- No more fucking thinking
from neither one of you!
All right, or else I will burn your asses
and snort your asses.
Now get the fuck out of here, beat it.
Nigga, and do something
with your head, nigga,
get out of here!
That nigga real mad right now.
What make a motherfucker
take his real teeth
and put, I don't understand that shit.
You're just a misunderstood genius.
Dad is gonna kick ass.
He doesn't like dogs in the
house in the first place.
All right. I told you so.
- He'll be fine, don't worry.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hey.
Hi, Mom.
Tia, what's this?
It's a dog.
Yeah, I can see that.
Why'd you let her bring
it in in the first place?
She's hardheaded,
you know she don't listen to me.
Excuse me.
Let me see if I've got this right.
Not only do I have to feed
the three mouths I've got,
plus Maurice the bottomless pit,
I have to feed this stray dog, too?
Bones, it's not nice to
bite the hand that feeds you.
What did you call him?
Bones.
You cannot keep that dog.
Hey, hey,
hey, what's up, Jimmy B?
What's going on, blood?
I got it all arranged
for you tonight, Jimmy.
Eddie Mack's gonna be there,
and Officer Koruptsky, too.
Got it all laid out for you, baby.
Well they've got 12 minutes, tops.
Jimmy, trust me on this, man.
There's some big money behind this, baby.
Not just big, I mean big business big,
like big corporation big,
big government big, Jimmy.
One word, three little letters.
Y-e-s, that's all it's gonna take.
We can move out of this
dump, hit the big time.
Big houses, legitimate
businesses, the works, baby.
That's your dream, not mine.
I don't ever wanna leave this street.
Never.
Status quo is totally cool with me, baby.
I hear you, Jimmy.
I'm with you, baby.
- Be good.
- All right, baby.
Yeah, I hear you, Jimmy.
You got all the status,
and I ain't got nothing but the quo.
Officer Lupovich, AKA Loopy Lou.
Not your style, is it, Eddie Mack?
Killing off your customers?
I ain't killed nobody.
Want me to rack them up?
You wanna play a game or what?
Too bad, no time to play today.
Got your tip.
Confiscated the whole stash.
That's fair enough, for the shit.
Don't you think I deserve
something a little extra
for knocking out the competition?
Shit, you was just doing
your motherfucking job.
The last thing you need
is for me to start doing my fucking job.
Give that motherfucker the money.
That's more like it.
That's the cost of doing business.
Maybe you can deduct it on your taxes.
Fuck you.
Lupovich, what's up with
Jeremiah selling that building?
What?
That's ridiculous, Patrick.
So how exactly did crack
get in the ghetto, Pop?
By magic?
How did it fly in there?
Like the man said, we
don't own that many planes.
Stop poisoning your mind
with that ghetto paranoia.
That's all just the ways of people
justifying their own failure.
No, no, no, Dad,
the man has been lying to
us for a hundred years.
Thank you.
I'm still waiting for
my 40 acres and a mule.
You gonna be waiting.
Son, you wouldn't know a
mule if one bit you in the ass.
Personally, I don't need a mule.
I've got myself a Lexus.
And nobody gave it to me.
- I wanna see the news.
- Please, Pops.
I'd like to see the news, please.
The strange disappearance
of those two state college
fraternity brothers.
- Patrick, I'm telling you...
- Their car, a 1999 Viper...
Patrick.
Slick.
What is that, what's that all about?
Nothing.
That was what, what were you gonna say?
Some terrible shit, Pops.
You better watch your mouth, boy.
Now look, those boys had no business
messing around down there.
You go places where
you're not meant to be,
and that's what you get.
Isn't that your old hood, Pops?
Yes, that's my old hood,
and it took some doing
to get out of there.
You just be glad that I did,
so you can start your life
here instead of down there.
Shouldn't we maybe be down there?
Doing something about
it, making it better?
It can't be done, Patrick!
That place has already
died and gone to hell.
Want me to get that, honey?
No, I'll get it.
Al Lupovich, long time no see.
I'll be just a second, honey.
What the fuck do you want?
Wanted to visit with my old pal J-Bird.
Don't call me that.
That's quite a brood you got there.
Regular Rainbow Coalition.
What the hell do you want, Lupovich?
You sold the building.
- What building?
- Don't shit a shitter.
What building, our building.
You were supposed to
sit on it, not sell it.
I didn't sell it.
Well somebody bought
it, so somebody sold it.
Not my problem.
That's a bozo no-no, J-Bird.
Even if they find
anything, it's been 20 years.
They could never trace it back to us.
Well you better hope not,
'cause it's like they say,
four can keep a secret if three are dead.
- Really?
- Daddy?
Hey, Tia.
I'm just talking to a
friend, I'll be right in.
Okay.
Nice rack.
How old is she?
Does she, you know?
That's my daughter, Lupovich.
Get the fuck off my property.
Your daughter.
Nice to see you.
You fat bastard.
Son of a bitch.
Yo, got it.
- And twist.
- All right.
I don't know what we're gonna do
with this place, boy.
It's all good.
It's ugly, but it's home.
You know that's bad luck, right?
That place is bad luck.
Why's that?
I don't know, goes way back.
Or so my mother says.
What else does your mama say?
You know, nothing much.
If I told you, you'd think she was crazy.
And one thing my mother is not is crazy.
- Okay.
So?
All right.
Can't believe I'm telling you this.
My mother says that every
house is two houses.
Every street, two streets.
Two's good.
There's a whole city, a whole world,
kinda beside, kinda on top.
Just below the city of the dead.
There's this invisible wall,
a fabric that keeps things separate.
Lucky thing.
Sure is, but when something bad happens,
something really bad,
the wall breaks, it tears.
And the dead get out?
Or the living fall in.
Who knows?
And you believe her?
If I did, do you think I would come
within 50 yards of your door?
Get out!
Patrick.
Y'all better stop messing around!
Go, boy.
Yo, what the fuck!
Freak!
What's the matter, bro?
Are you spooked?
No.
Yeah, okay, maybe just
a little, all right?
Hey, I know.
There is kind of a
strange vibe up in here.
Make yourself
comfortable around the circle.
- Let me sit right here.
- We will begin
in just a moment.
You gonna join us?
Can't, gotta finish this for school.
You know, God gave you the vision.
I hate to see you waste it
on painting pretty pictures.
You got your vision and I got mine,
and I'm not gonna waste mine like you did.
Sorry, Mama.
Maybe next time?
I don't want you to go
to that house anymore,
and I want you to stay
away from those kids,
and stay away from that dog.
That dog is a servant of evil.
Ever been inside?
Yeah, back in the day.
Before it became what it is.
And what's that?
It's a bad place, and a door to worse.
I gots to TCB tonight,
so I should be through about 7:00.
Come see me.
Can't I get there early
and give you some good luck?
No, baby, you know I don't need no luck.
I'm just letting them have
their say before I tell them no.
All right, let me see your hands.
- Come on, baby.
- Come on,
let me see your hands.
- Come on, baby.
- Come on.
Please?
All that reading,
advising, shining mess,
that was your mama's bag.
It was my mama's bag, and her grandmama,
and a long line of mamas before her.
Well it sounds like Mama
needs a brand new bag.
Come on, let me see your hands, please?
Now your left hand is the past,
your right hand is the
present and the future.
Now this is your life line, and this...
Jimmy, there's a line
across your life line.
It must be my clothesline.
Maybe my phone line.
Jimmy, I'm serious!
Cancel the meeting, don't go, okay?
Stay with me.
Don't you worry about nothing, baby.
These hands of mine are gonna
be stroking your neck tonight.
Jimmy, please!
Pearl, trust me.
Thought you might be needing some help.
Look at this,
man, it looks like blood.
Yeah, the floor's throbbing.
Snap.
Yo, it feels like a heartbeat.
It's just a problem in the plumbing.
You're probably right,
but I'm gonna check it out,
and y'all are coming with me.
Come on.
Damn.
Now what is this?
Look at this, man.
Yo Maurice,
what you think that is?
It's rust, yo.
Rust never sleeps.
You call that rust?
All right, now where does this go?
Don't ask me.
Now what?
Eat that spinach, boy.
There you go, you got it.
I'm not going down there.
Go ahead, Tia.
I'm right behind you.
Don't get behind me.
It's just some flies, y'all,
come on.
What is that smell?
What'd you expect, Cynthia?
Where there's smoke, there's fire,
where there's flies, there's shit.
Disgusting!
Space that's so perfect
for a recording studio?
Maurice, not now, just shut up, man.
- Chill out.
- You know something,
he got a point, though.
It's just gonna take a little more work
than I thought, that's all.
Think about it.
Put down a real floor, put
some dampening on the wall.
We'll have totally controlled
sound, it'll be perfect.
Yeah.
We'll make our first record
where no one can hear us scream.
Be afraid, be very afraid.
Oh my God!
Oh shit.
Yo, give me some light.
Hello.
Who are you?
Ladies and
gentlemen, boys and girls,
I'd like you to meet Jimmy Bones.
What are you talking about?
This is the story of,
this is the story of Jimmy Bones,
black as night and hard as stone.
Gold-plated deuce like the king of Siam,
got a switchblade loose
and a diamond on his hand.
- Talking bullshit.
- There's the switchblade
and there's the diamond, man.
- I'm telling you.
- You telling me
this could be him or not?
Damn, it's so fresh.
Put that thing down!
What are you doing, you can't take that.
Might be evidence.
Evidence of what?
Gee, Patrick, doesn't
it seem a little odd to you
that he would stab himself in the chest
and then bury himself, too?
Yeah, I agree.
Bones, settle down.
Gotta do something about the dog.
What we have to do,
Patrick, is call the police.
Right, you know, for someone so cute,
you're so stupid sometimes.
Call the police, we don't get a permit.
We can't just leave him, can we?
- Yes, we can.
- What?!
He ain't going nowhere.
We will deal with
this after the weekend.
Let's go, let's go!
Fuck it, whatever,
whatever, whatever!
You put your fingers all over it!
Maurice, I'm gonna leave you down here.
Coming!
Cyn?
What?
You all right?
Yeah.
Come on, let's go.
- Patrick, what up?
- I'm coming.
Come on.
Okay, I'm coming.
I guess he won't be needing this.
Or this.
Well, you know she doesn't want me here.
With you, in this house.
Whatever.
It's true, she doesn't
trust you, and neither do I.
I can handle your mother.
- No, you can't.
- Yes, I can.
No, you can't.
She will love me, watch.
- No, she won't.
- Trust me.
See, but the X-factor is your daddy.
I don't know nothing about him.
Neither do I.
I never met him.
She won't talk about him, ever.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
It's okay, I'm not sad about it.
It's life, you know?
I've never known him, so
it's totally normal to me.
I'm not doing too well with this.
Yeah, you are.
Patrick, stop.
What?
I can't.
All right.
Do you want me to take you home?
No, I wanna stay with
you guys, it's just...
No, no, no.
You don't have to explain, I understand.
I'll go sleep with the guys.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Night.
Welcome, my brothers and my sisters.
We will begin with our hymn.
The spirit world
is all around us at this moment,
and the dearly departed are here,
among us, pressing around us.
It's okay, you can stay.
But no getting fresh.
This is nice.
There is a spirit among us.
Who has just joined our circle?
Lordy, what is that smell?
Stop.
Patrick, cut it out.
Does someone wanna send a message?
Knock once for yes and twice for no.
Is it someone in our circle?
Stop.
Is it Miss Lillian?
Cut it out.
Is the message for Miss Abernathy?
Patrick, stop.
Is the message for me?
Stop!
No, Jimmy!
No!
Patrick, stop!
What's wrong?
Cynthia, Cynthia!
That sounds like your mom.
Cynthia, open up this door!
Open up this door, Cynthia!
What are you doing?
Where's my daughter?
I wanna see her now!
If you hold on a
moment, I will go upstairs,
and I'll see...
Cynthia, come on out here!
I know she's in there!
Cynthia, Cynthia!
Oh, God, come on.
Come on, baby.
You're okay, come on.
Come on, we gotta get out of here.
If you stay in this house one more night,
you might as well be just
sleeping in your grave!
Come on.
You certainly have a
way with women, Patrick.
Well, we're in business.
What?
Where we going?
You know I hate surprises.
It's a little business
venture that I made on my own,
I wanted to show you.
I think you will approve.
I hope so.
What are we doing down here?
Like you always said,
we need to look for
the undervalued, right?
Don't get no more undervalued than this.
Come on, Pop.
Just come on, come on, come on!
I bet you didn't know that
your company owned this place.
I went through a broker, so
that you didn't know it was me,
but I couldn't wait to see your face
when you saw how I fixed it up.
Look at this.
Son, is this some kind of sick joke?
No!
Look, Pop.
You listen to me, boy.
I didn't work all of my goddamn life
to get out of this neighborhood
for you to move right back in it!
I thought you'd be proud of me.
I'm just trying to do what you did,
take nothing and make something out of it.
Nobody will ever come down here, son.
Look at this fucking neighborhood!
Son, shut it down.
Shut it down.
The company will buy it back.
No.
Nuh, not this time, Pop.
Look, I did this on my own,
and we will open tonight.
Bullshit!
That is bullshit!
You sell it back, and
that is a fucking order!
Do you fucking hear me?
Shut it!
You shut it, god damn it!
You shut it down and you sell this fucker!
Shut it, Patrick!
What's going on, baby?
What's going on, player?
Jimmy's into it, man,
that's what I'm saying.
Jimmy's into it, just wait.
Hey Jimmy, what's happening, baby?
- Good to see you.
- Hey, what's up, J-Bird?
You remember Eddie Mack, don't you?
Yeah, we met.
Yeah, we used to do the
little afterschool b-ball thing
at Kenwood.
What it is, homeboy?
What it will be.
Hey Jimmy, you know
Officer Lupovich, right?
Yeah, I've heard of him.
Yeah, man, you got
a nice crib here, man.
It's nice to see a
black man doing so well.
Yeah, we happy, everybody's
happy, we do all right.
But you know things change.
You gotta think ahead.
Got them lotteries all over now, Bonesy.
Starting here, too, maybe next year.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Jimmy.
A lot of our old customers
getting their new people
to cross the state lines,
buying those lotto tickets.
We need to get on this thing
fast, know what I'm saying?
What do anybody want with
them damn lottery tickets, man?
What else, young blood?
Money.
Oh no, man, it ain't the money.
It's the high, you know?
The big fat floating what if?
And dig, man, it's way
more profitable, man.
Nobody ever wins, so you never pay out.
But a $2 bet is cheaper than a $20 bag.
Yeah, yeah, I can dig that, man,
but I'm not talking horse.
I'm talking a $5 kick in the head,
that's a quick ticket to Heaven, man.
And fools keep coming back?
That's right, baby.
Those fools?
They're my people.
I can dig that, man, but
it ain't no thing, man.
It's just a poor man's freebase.
Check it out.
I ain't interested,
and if you gonna sell it,
don't sell it around here.
Man, here, just try it, man, all right?
I said no thanks.
Come on, man, try this, man,
- it ain't gonna kill you!
- Hey, huggy bear!
I done drove all this way, man!
Back off.
Sit down!
That's cool, I'm copasteady.
But it's like this here, man.
It's a wave coming, man.
A big-ass, Krakatoa, east of Java wave.
Now either you gonna be on top,
up here in chocolate heaven,
or you gonna get caught
up in the muddy undertow.
And that's real.
That's beautiful, baby.
Totally widescreen,
sci-fi forward thinking,
and I can dig that.
But that's for you and yours.
Me and mines, we cool as
a motherfucking icicle
in a freezer.
Oh yeah, by the way, your
12 and a half minutes is up.
Hey, sorry about that, J-Bird.
It's never business, it's always pleasure.
It's cool, Jimmy.
You see this motherfucker?
- No, no, no.
- Fuck it, cool.
No, no, no, man, fine.
- Hey, Jimmy, look.
- Yeah, baby?
Just hear me out on this one.
Pass up the money train
and jump his ass on the bus.
His loss.
- Hear me out on this.
- We don't need nothing
like that over here, man, we cool.
Drop the piece, homeboy.
- Drop the piece, nigger!
- Wait, what's going on?
Eddie Mack, come on, baby!
Lupovich, baby, just be cool.
Everybody just be cool.
Come on, baby, be cool.
Be cool, man.
Jimmy, man, just hear it out,
man, just hear out the deal.
I don't need to hear no deal.
I don't need no new partners,
I don't need no new product,
and I damn sure don't need
this cracker's Saturday
night special in my face.
Just try it, Jimmy, that's all.
You heard the man.
Try it.
All right, Jimmy, all
right, baby, that's good.
Hit it up.
Yeah.
Like that, Jimmy?
Just let it kick in, baby.
It's gonna be nice, Jimmy.
Jimmy?
Oh my God!
- Oh, god!
- Oh shit.
Damn it!
Jimmy!
Man, you done fucked up!
- Stop right there!
- One good suit!
God damn it!
- Tell her to shut up!
- No, no, no.
Get your punk ass over there now!
Somebody tell that
bitch to stop screaming.
Hey, I said stop fucking
screaming, you hear me?
Lou, Lou, Lou!
What fuck are we gonna do now?
Just shut up and let me think here!
God damn it, I need this
like I fucking need a hole in my head.
I am not the only one in this room
with that nigger's blood on my hands.
Get his knife.
All right, everybody leaves a print.
We hang together or we hang separately.
Now cut him, and cut him good.
What it is, homeboy?
What it will be, nigger.
Oh god, oh shit.
Now you.
J-Bird, help me, brother.
I'm sorry, brother.
Since we was grasshoppers.
Like you said, Jimmy.
Every man for himself, baby.
Hey, Shaft, it's your turn.
Hey, don't even think about it.
Man, hurry up!
Okay, mama, it's your turn.
I won't do it.
Either you cut him, or die with him.
I love you.
All right, let's clean this shit up.
Take this and bury it with him.
Come on, move!
Get him out of here.
I bet you wish you would've
took the deal now, nigga?
Damn!
Does your mama know that you're here?
What my mama don't know won't hurt her.
I heard that.
Hey, can you take a little
extended solo right about now,
funk soul brother?
What does she look like, Maurice?
Thanks, bro.
Baby, if you ain't got any culture in you,
you're about to have all of them.
Breathing just gets deeper, baby.
Your sweet little gangsta del amore.
We will speak the
international language of love.
Yo, bro!
Patrick!
What?
I gotta see what he wants.
I know you're having a good time,
but can you please go
find the gangsta of love?
I'm getting vinyl spindonitis,
and I know he's upstairs.
All right, keep an eye on Cyn for me.
Thank you.
Yo Maurice, where you at?
Maurice!
Yo, man, get decent, 'cause I'm coming in.
Maurice.
Come on, man.
Oh my God.
My God.
The gangster of love
don't eat no fried chicken.
Oh shit!
Fuck!
Where you going?
No, don't run, relax!
Don't run, relax!
Stay calm, don't push!
Hey, don't push!
Relax!
Don't push, please!
Settle down!
What the hell's going on?
- Come on!
- Where's Maurice?
He's dead, get up!
Move, come on!
Get out of here, go!
Go!
Run, run!
I guess you won't be needing this.
Or this, motherfucker.
It's okay.
We're safe.
Cynthia, Cynthia.
You know, we should've
done this a long time ago.
It's all right,
baby, it's all right.
He tried to kill us.
If he wanted to kill you,
you would've been dead already.
Who is he?
What was he?
Your father.
He was your father.
You have his eyes.
Free at last, free at last.
No!
Leave me be!
It wasn't my fault, man.
I didn't know what they'd planned.
Hush.
It don't even matter now.
Lookie here, man.
It's me, baby, it's me.
I been on your side all the way.
Don't you remember, man?
Remember?
I'll show you what I remember.
Feel better?
I had no choice.
What else could I do?
You could've died
with me, or died trying.
You're gonna be free and clear, Shotgun.
All debts are paid, baby.
Hey, man, what's
happening, fellas?
Did you do it?
Do what, son?
What are you talking about?
You know what I'm talking about.
The club, did you do it?
I know you didn't want us down there.
I wouldn't have risked
killing you to get you out.
I was trying to protect you.
From what?
Why?
Why did you give a shit
about the building?
Why did you care that we
were there, of all places?
It is just a bad neighborhood, Patrick!
Bullshit.
Look, don't lie to me, Pop.
Come on, for once, tell me the truth.
Look, I saw your face.
Now you knew that place,
and you knew those people!
It's the past, Patrick, it's dead.
Dead?
I don't think your past is dead, Pop.
It's alive.
And it killed Maurice.
Hey, slinky dink.
Are you looking to score?
Little brother.
I got a natural high, a supernatural high.
You got a supernatural high?
Well look, Eddie Mack don't like no wackos
coming through our neighborhood
playing that rain man stuff, okay?
Big badass Eddie Mack,
got shit for brains, and that's a fact.
Are you suffering from negligence?
I'll whoop your ass!
Hold up, shit, that nigga crazy, man.
He ain't shit.
This nigga's suffering from negligence.
Look here, you fake-ass Shaft,
why don't you raise up off
that coat and let me have that?
Sure, here it is.
Mama?
Oh honey.
He's gonna kill every one of
them, every last one of them.
Kill who?
Eddie Mack, that cop, and Jeremiah.
And those kids.
Maybe they deserved it.
Maybe we all deserve it.
Patrick doesn't.
And his brother and sister don't.
I don't.
I'll try something.
I have nothing left to lose.
Only you.
This what you want, right?
It tickles!
I wanna do that again.
All night?
I gotta go winky.
Fucked around and got
me a Marilyn Monroe ho.
Play that rolling bass, baby.
I'm gonna tickle your little
pink tweeter all night.
Put these snakes to work, move your body.
Nothing wrong.
Yeah, hey, hey.
Hey, Snowflake!
Where you at, girl?
I got something to tell you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Snowflake!
Come on, now, girl, don't
nobody stand up the mack daddy.
Snowflake!
Look here, girl, where you at?
Come on, now, baby, I got
something to give you!
Snowflake!
All right, come on, now,
bitch, quit playing now.
I don't wanna play these
type of games, come on.
Oh shit, I almost broke...
The fuck?
Snowflake?
All right, motherfucker,
y'all wanna do this shit?
Motherfuckers wanna act ignorant?
Where the fuck you at?
You wanna jump, motherfucker?
You wanna be froggy, nigger?
Leap!
Jimmy Bones, is that you?
We killed you, motherfucker,
and buried your ass
in nothing but your bitch's bloody rags.
Now I can count the holes
in your motherfucking chest.
Is that it?
Your big-ass tidal wave?
You think I'm gonna do it?
Think I'm gonna do it?
Fuck you, Jimmy, you jive-ass nigga.
- Yeah.
- Man, where the fuck
are you at?
I'm here, where the fuck are you?
Man, I'm at the spot
where I said I was gonna be.
Now get your ass over here!
All right, I'll meet you there.
Bones.
Bones, you motherfucker,
what you done done to me?
Not half of what I'm planning on.
Man, this is some twisted shit, man.
What you need with my head?
I'm just using it to
carry your soul, sucker.
My soul, fuck you.
I killed you, you killed me, we even!
Damn, why you gotta get all
meta-fucking-physical, nigga?
Shit!
I'm sick...
You just gonna bang my
shit up against the wall?
Jesus fucking Christ, I need this
like I fucking need a hole in my head.
Oh yeah, you better be scared.
What?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
You heard the man, try it.
You next, Lou.
I told your ass, boy.
You wanna get ahead in life.
Now was that fucking necessary, man?
What's up with these gates?
Let's see if these
gates can save Jeremiah
when his past comes calling.
We have to save him.
Save who?
Can Jeremiah come out and play?
What it is, and what
it will be, my brother.
And it will be your ass.
How the hell did you get in here?
At a time like this, is that
what you really wanna know?
How the fuck I got in here?
Oh my God, Jimmy.
Dad!
What the hell are you guys doing?
Somebody please tell me...
Yeah, right.
Makes me feel better.
Where are you going?
I just called 911.
Then we really gotta go,
'cause I can't explain this, all right?
I'll be back, hopefully with Dad.
Wait, I'm coming with you.
No, you're not, you gotta stay with Mom!
Patrick!
Jesus fucking Christ,
what is this place?
- Oh my God!
- Shut the fuck up.
You two bitches were just meat.
Never had any idea smarter
than getting yourselves a little bit more.
But my brother J-Bird
here, this nigga was smart.
He didn't just want more.
He wanted more with compound interest.
Come on, Jimmy, please, man.
Get Lou.
Yeah, get him, Jimmy.
Get him, get that motherfucker.
Bye, Loopy Lou!
The blood, it's the blood.
- What, Mama?
- Remember when I told you
that a person, has more than
two parts, they have three?
Body, soul, and spirit?
Well the spirit lives in the blood,
and the spirit keeps the
body and soul together,
and sometimes the spirit lives on.
Jimmy's blood must still
be in that building.
Let's go.
Now look here, Jimmy,
I got $20,000, baby,
saved up, buried.
Don't nobody know where it is but me.
You can have half of it.
All right, look here, Jimmy.
You can have it all, man, just Jimmy.
No, Jimmy, come on, man.
Jimmy, Jimmy!
Come on, man, Jimmy!
And now, J-Bird, my brother,
it's time for you to
collect your interest.
This is it.
We found that skeleton right down here.
All right, it was here, right here!
What'd he have on?
- Nothing.
- No, wait, wait.
There was a green rag.
My god, my dress.
My bloody dress, we gotta burn
it, we gotta close the door.
We gotta find my dress!
The blood on the dress
is keeping him alive!
Not gonna find anything!
Look for it!
You was my main man.
Since we was grasshoppers.
I always looked after you.
You had a piece of everything I had.
I didn't want a piece of yours, Jimmy.
I wanted my own.
And fuck everybody else?
Oh, god damn, Jimmy!
Think about it, Jimmy.
If it had happened to you,
you would've done the
same goddamn thing, man.
Nah, brother.
I wouldn't have done any
man the way you did me.
It's a trip, ain't it?
Oh my God.
Are you all right?
Baby, you okay?
She's all right, she's all right.
Be careful!
Oh no, hell no, hell
no, hell no, hell no!
Bill, slow down, be careful.
Don't get hurt, be careful.
Oh shit.
Watch your step.
Stay back.
- No!
- Mama!
Mama!
Come back!
Find Jeremiah!
No!
Mama, come back!
Tell me, Jimmy, what will it take?
What do you want?
Just tell me, Jimmy, just tell me!
Oh man, that's easy.
Think you can give me my life back?
Can you swing that, brother?
You know I can't do that, Jimmy.
- You know I can't do that!
- Fuck it, then!
Dog eat dog, brother.
Dog eat dog.
We can climb out.
Climb to where?
Anywhere but here.
Come on, man, let's go.
Turn around, baby.
You know I always loved you in this dress.
Damn.
Come on, give me your hand.
Look out, you cool?
All right.
Did he create all this?
No, but he's a part of it.
This is the city of the dead.
We just have to remember
what was here and follow it.
Those stairs should take
us to the second floor.
Didn't I tell you, baby?
Didn't I tell you I'd be
stroking your neck tonight?
I took out my revenge 'cause I had to.
Now stay here with me, forever.
Okay, where do we go now?
Not now.
Come on!
Oh my God.
- Maurice.
Bro, where you going?
Maurice, where you going?
Bill, wait!
That's not Maurice.
Maurice!
Maurice.
Where you going, man?
Maurice, where the hell you at?
Bill!
He's gone.
This way.
Cynthia,
wait, I gotta find Bill.
Welcome home, baby girl.
Cynthia, no, wait.
Cyn, wait!
Patrick!
Pull me out of here!
Help me, Patrick, please!
Dad?
Please, Patrick.
Oh no, Dad.
Help me, Patrick!
Help me, will you?
Jimmy Bones did this, Patrick!
Jimmy Bones did this!
Help me, Patrick!
Help me!
Surprise, nigga.
Die!
Die, motherfucker, die!
Stop it!
Stop it, please!
Daddy, let him go!
Daddy, stop!
Mama, make him stop!
Jimmy!
I love you.
No!
Mama!
Oh my God!
Oh my god!
No, Mom, no!
- Get away!
- Cyn, come on!
No, let go of me!
- No!
- We gotta go now!
Come on, run, let's go!
Come on, run, Cyn, run!
All right, we have to jump!
I can't!
We have to, now!
Cyn, come on!
Cynthia!
Come on, jump, hurry up!
Are you all right?
Come on, baby, we gotta go!
Come on, go, go, go!
Oh, shit!
Dog eat dog, boy.
Dog eat dog.